hi spring fans welcome to another super
嗨，春季粉丝们欢迎来到另一个超级
quick mid midseason interregnum
中赛季快中场间
installment of spring tips we're and I
我们和我的 spring 技巧 的分期付款
want to talk about something that is
想谈谈是
super super preliminary I wouldn't
超级超级初步我不会
recommend it for production but I think
推荐用于生产，但我认为
all all the same very interesting it is
都一样非常有趣
a third-party community project called
一个名为“第三方社区”的项目
JA sync which now has preliminary
JA sync现在已经初步
support for my sequel now again when i
现在，当我再次支持我的续集时
go to production with this tomorrow
明天去生产
probably not but it'll get there
可能不会，但是会到达那里
eventually right RTB see of course is
最终正确的实时出价当然是
the reactive relational database
反应型关系数据库
connectivity API it's an SPI that
连接API是一个SPI
provides the reactive primitives for
为以下提供反应性原语
working with a sequel data store and I
使用续集数据存储，我
did a whole video on this a whole hour
整整一个小时做了一个完整的视频
long thing inducing you know every
诱使你知道的长事
different sort of tiered ways to use our
使用我们的不同层次方法
TBC and what it does and all that stuff
TBC及其作用以及所有这些东西
and I don't intend to reproduce all that
我不打算复制所有这些
here just to introduce one new thing but
这里只是介绍一件新东西，但是
quick rehash it's a very basic SPI that
快速重述这是一个非常基本的SPI
has a number of different
有很多不同
implementations namely post squares in
实现方式是在
h2 and Microsoft sequel server and one
h2和Microsoft续集服务器和一台
of the common questions I've been given
给出的一些常见问题
when I'm out there talking to the
当我在外面和
community which is is there support for
有支持的社区
my sequel my sequel is Ubiquiti I'm not
我的续集我的续集是Ubiquiti我不是
really a huge fan if I'm honest I don't
如果我说实话，我真的是个超级粉丝
really use it if I can avoid it so I was
如果我能避免使用它，我会使用它
not heartbroken that it wasn't among the
没伤心的是它不在
first databases to be supported but I
首先要支持的数据库，但我
concede that it is a very popular
承认这是一个非常受欢迎的
database and so I wanted to show you how
数据库，所以我想向您展示
to use it right so you can so you can
正确使用它，以便您可以
see if this is an opportunity for you to
看看这是否是您的机会
be able to take advantage of this this
能够利用这个
functionality and it's kind of
功能，有点
interesting it's coming from a third
有趣的是它来自三分之一
party project right this just sync
派对项目，就这样同步
project has done a heck of a job
项目做得很辛苦
supporting my sequel but they did it in
支持我的续集，但他们做到了
terms of an asynchronous API it's not a
异步API的术语，它不是
reactive API right so if you look at
正确的反应式API，所以如果您看一下
their API there's completable futures
他们的API有可替代的未来
and and these kinds of things right but
而且这些事情对但
there is now preliminary support here
现在这里有初步的支持
for our two DBC or two thing is super
因为我们两个DBC或两件事超级好
compelling super interesting so that
引人入胜的超级有趣，这样
builds upon the other stuff that's
建立在其他东西之上
already there so we're gonna we're gonna
已经在那里，所以我们要去
go ahead and just use that along with
继续使用，并与
spring data or TVC we have create a
spring data 或TVC，我们创建了一个
brand new project but as I said before
全新的项目，但正如我之前所说
and as remain
并保持
- these are not GA bits these are not
-这些不是GA位，这些不是
things you can go to the startup spring
你可以去启动 Spring 的事情
that I will speak initializer and get a
我会说初始化程序并得到一个
checkbox for so let's do reactive my
复选框，这样我们就可以进行反应了
sequel with sync and r2 DBC okay and all
同步和r2 DBC的续集还可以
I'm going to bring in is the reactive
我要带的是反应式
web support here just so that I have
网络支持在这里，以便我有
something to to keep the thread open
保持线程开放的东西
because I'm going to do a lot of
因为我要做很多事情
asynchronous stuff that might very well
异步的东西可能很好
finish after the main method of the Java
在Java的主要方法之后完成
process decides to end and and then take
过程决定结束，然后采取
my JVM program program with it okay so
我的JVM程序程序就可以了
hit generate and here we are
点击生成，我们在这里
for that try again
为此，再试一次
all right so there's the zip file open
好的，所以打开了zip文件
this up
这个
all righty a couple of nice things here
好吧，这里有几件好事
it's just a regular simple little
这只是一个普通的简单小
program I'm not gonna introduce
我不会介绍的程序
everything altogether but I want to I
所有的一切，但我想我
want to talk to my sequel so the first
想和我续集谈谈
thing is I need a my secret instance and
我需要一个我的秘密实例，
if I'm honest with you in preparing for
如果我对你诚实的准备
this video this was the hardest part for
这部影片是最难的部分
me because I don't have my sequel
我，因为我没有续集
running in my local machine and it's
在我的本地计算机上运行
been you know a long time since I
自从我知道你已经很久了
bothered to write I'm sure I I'm sure
麻烦写我确定我确定
I've done it a few times the last couple
我已经完成了最后几次
of years but not on my day to day
年，但不是我的日常
experience it certainly so I had to dig
一定要经历一下，所以我不得不去挖
up the same can incantation to create a
一样可以咒骂创建一个
darker instance to get it working so
较暗的实例使其正常工作
basically I'm creating a named container
基本上我正在创建一个命名容器
called orders my sequel to be I'm
叫命令我的续集是我
binding the container port to the host
将容器端口绑定到主机
port I'm giving it some environment
端口我给它一些环境
variables namely the host I want to bind
变量即我要绑定的主机
to everything I want the root password
我想要的所有root密码
I want the regular user just a regular
我希望普通用户只是普通用户
user called orders a regular user
被称为订购普通用户的用户
password call orders and they database
密码呼叫订单及其数据库
call orders and I want to use the five
电话订单，我想使用这五个
that X series of my sequel instances
X系列续集实例
that said my sequel 8 is out right it
说我的续集8就对了
just it just dropped a few weeks ago I
就在几周前
haven't tried this with that because you
还没有尝试过，因为你
know go with what I know right so I
知道我所知道的正确，所以我
figured out to stay with this Oracle
想出要留在这个甲骨文
changed in compatibly some things in
改变了某些东西
Oracle my sequel 8 decks including
甲骨文我的续集8套，包括
authentication and I'm sure the change
身份验证，我确定会有所更改
is worthwhile I'm sure there's a good
值得，我确定
reason for it I just haven't had the
原因就是我还没有
time to dig into it and to see if that
时间去研究它，看看是否
works with this and and so on so being
与此一起工作，依此类推
more pragmatic I figured more people are
更务实的我想更多的人是
more than likely dollars to know it
知道它的可能性超过美元
dollars to doughnuts they're gonna be
美元将成为甜甜圈
using this five direct series at the
使用这五个直接系列
moment so we'll use that and I already
那一刻，我们将使用它，而我已经
got that docker instance running on my
让那个docker实例在我的计算机上运行
local machine so then you can just
本地计算机，这样您就可以
execute that that will drop you into the
执行该操作将使您进入
container and there you know I can I can
容器，在那里你知道我可以
talk to the database to orders orders
与数据库对话以订购订单
h-12 7.0
h-12 7.0
I'm 0.1 now come on and minus P okay so
我现在是0.1来减去P好吧，所以
if I do this I can show databases and
如果我这样做，我可以显示数据库和
use orders show tables describe orders
使用订单显示表描述订单
okay so you can see I've got a single
好吧，你可以看到我有一个
solitary table called orders with an ID
称为ID的订单的单独表格
and a first name column the ID is a long
还有一个名字列，ID长
in Java big int and my sequel in sequel
在Java big int和我的续集中
and a var carved for the name okay just
和一个刻有名字的变种就好了
trivial but it's enough to get us a
琐碎，但足以让我们
hello world which is all really care to
你好，世界真的很在乎
have so in order to use it of course I
为了使用它当然有
need the right dependencies and again
需要正确的依赖关系
there's no spring in your size or
你的尺码没有Spring 或
support here so I'm just gonna add this
支持这里，所以我要添加这个
the old-fashioned way
老式的方式
I'm gonna add some code to my build here
我要在这里添加一些代码
and that will come from here so I'm a
那将来自这里，所以我是
little cheat sheet I'll add the
小备忘单，我将添加
dependencies the repositories and we are
依赖存储库，我们
okay so I'm adding J Center I'm adding
好的，所以我要添加J Center
spring the snapshot in spring lives
Spring 的生活快照
milestone and I'm now gonna add the my
里程碑，我现在要添加我的
sequel dependencies for just Inc and the
只是Inc和
spring data support okay so I'm being
spring数据支持好吧，我正在
I'm bringing in spring data or TBC which
我要输入 spring data 或TBC
is built against a github snapshot I
是针对github快照构建的
mean this is probably super fragile I
这可能是我非常脆弱
wouldn't I wouldn't depend on this for
我不会因为这个
production code I wouldn't even depend
我什至不依赖的生产代码
sure if it'll work next week right let's
确定下周是否会成功吧，让我们
just say that but it is interesting I
只是这么说，但我很有趣
want to share it so here we are and this
想要分享，所以我们在这里
is the JA sink or to see my sequel API
是JA接收器还是看我的续集API
again you can use the r2 BC support
再次，您可以使用r2 BC支持
today more readily the spring data stuff
今天更容易获得 spring data 资料
is the thing that might might change
可能会改变的东西
from here to there but this is already
从这里到那里，但这已经是
pretty solid I built a basic client and
相当扎实，我建立了一个基本的客户，
I'll make sure to check the basic are to
我将确保检查基本内容
BBC client into the git repository for
BBC客户端进入git存储库
the spring tip code here but we're just
Spring 的提示代码在这里，但我们只是
gonna do it we're gonna use it in terms
我们要做它，我们将在术语上使用它
of spring data and again I already did a
Spring 的数据，我已经做了一个
video on that so you can watch that one
影片，以便您观看
at length okay so
最后，好吧
in order for this to work I need some
为了这个工作，我需要一些
configuration right so class my sequel
配置正确，所以上课我的续集
application configuration extends
应用程序配置扩展
abstract our 2d BC configuration and
抽象我们的2d BC配置并
we're going to return a connection
我们要返回一个连接
factory and enable our TVC repositories
工厂并启用我们的TVC存储库
okay so we need to return a connection
好吧，我们需要返回一个连接
factor in the connection factory I've
我连接工厂的因素
I've cheated here I've got the code
我在这里骗了我有代码
laying around all right pretty
躺在周围好漂亮
straightforward so you're Kate adjusting
直截了当，所以您要凯特调整
connection factory using a my sequel
连接工厂使用我的续集
connection factory and then there's this
连接工厂，然后有这个
charmingly PHP like method parse or Die
迷人的PHP之类的方法解析或Die
right which I think it's kind of funny
对，我觉得这很有趣
and we're just connecting using using
我们只是使用using连接
what it looks like a just regular sort
它看起来像常规的那种
of my stable connection string so orders
我的稳定连接字符串的顺序
order this is the username password host
订购这是用户名密码主机
port database name okay and that's it
端口数据库名称就可以了
that's my connect that's my
那是我的连接那是我的
configuration everything else after that
之后配置其他所有内容
is of course just standard spring data
当然只是标准的Spring 数据
so let's do this interface order
所以让我们做这个接口顺序
repository
资料库
stenz reactive crud repository managing
Stenz反应堆存储库管理
entities of type order so okay that
订单类型的实体好
right now and that'll be tables orders
现在，那将是桌子订单
data logs constructor and orgs
数据日志构造函数和组织
constructor long ID string name
构造函数长ID字符串名称
and ID all right so here's this order
和ID没问题，所以这是此订单
long and that's it so it's a it's a
很长，就是这样，这是一个
repository managing instances of order
仓库管理订单实例
whose type is a type with primary keys
其类型是具有主键的类型
have typed long and I'm mapping it to a
输入了很长的时间，我正在将其映射到
table called orders even though the
该表称为订单，即使
entities called order singular so I used
实体称为订单单数，所以我用
a table annotation from spring data to
从spring数据到
do that these are of course Lombok
这些当然是龙目岛
compile-time annotations and really once
编译时注释，实际上只有一次
I've done that all I can do is I'm just
我已经做到了，我所能做的就是
going to kind of beam that listens for
去听的光束
the data right so I'm going to
正确的数据，所以我要
application run or I guess run I'm gonna
应用程序运行，或者我想运行
inject the order of posit story and I'll
注入假设故事的顺序，我将
just say args
只是说参数
pause story dot find all let's subscribe
暂停故事点，找到所有让我们订阅的内容
and I'm just gonna inject I'm gonna use
我只是要注射我要用
a logger here with Lombok okay all right
Lombok的记录器在这里好吧
good stuff alright so there's this very
好东西，所以这是非常
simple example and the application
简单的例子和​​应用
starts up I'm gonna print out everything
启动，我将打印出所有内容
in the database which will be mapped to
在将要映射到的数据库中
objects using reactive sequel my sequel
对象使用反应性续集我的续集
support okay let's see here we go
支持好吧，让我们看看这里，我们去
what did I do wrong oh this is called FN
我做错了什么哦，这就是FN
Prime I saw that I knew that order is a
总理，我知道我知道订单是
keyword and sequel some databases get
一些数据库获得的关键字和续集
upset when you use the token name as
使用令牌名称时感到不安
well so just to keep things interesting
好吧，只是为了让事情有趣
so there you go
所以你去了
there we are there's our data on the
那里有关于我们的数据
console is there more to be done of
控制台还有更多要做的事情
course but I think this is super
当然，但我认为这是超级
interesting and I wanted to call
有趣，我想打电话
people's attention to it I hope you
人们的关注，希望你
enjoyed this to go check out my old
喜欢这个去看看我的旧
video my video from like no no no more
视频我的视频来自不再，不再，不再
than a few months at most
最多不超过几个月
that introduces our TBC and reactive
介绍我们的TBC和反应式
sequel data access in the spring
Spring 的续集数据访问
ecosystem that one is done in terms of
就以下方面而言已完成的生态系统
postgrads but again it's nice to see
研究生，但很高兴看到
that we have you know heavy hitters like
我们有你知道重击手
my sequel and Microsoft sequel server
我的续集和Microsoft续集服务器
and of course post guys all well
当然，大家都很好
supported down thanks for that and as
支持下来，为此
always we'll see you next time
总是我们下次见
you
您